[{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678877852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7489,"timeElapsed":36772},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678880339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":39259},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678886653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":6312,"timeElapsed":45573},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678895066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8412,"timeElapsed":53986},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678900981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5912,"timeElapsed":59901},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678905388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4406,"timeElapsed":64308},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678914701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":9311,"timeElapsed":73621},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678920092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5390,"timeElapsed":79012},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678924514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4420,"timeElapsed":83434},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678930452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4693,"timeElapsed":89372},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678933929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3474,"timeElapsed":92849},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678937330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3400,"timeElapsed":96250},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678942478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5147,"timeElapsed":101398},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678945422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2942,"timeElapsed":104342},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678949154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3731,"timeElapsed":108074},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678951448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2292,"timeElapsed":110368},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678956318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4869,"timeElapsed":115238},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678957923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1605,"timeElapsed":116843},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678963679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4500,"timeElapsed":122599},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678968054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4372,"timeElapsed":126974},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678972238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4183,"timeElapsed":131158},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678976889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4650,"timeElapsed":135809},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678980121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3231,"timeElapsed":139041},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678983699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3577,"timeElapsed":142619},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678985964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2262,"timeElapsed":144884},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678991285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":5320,"timeElapsed":150205},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678993935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2649,"timeElapsed":152855},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679001941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":6511,"timeElapsed":160861},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679004198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2254,"timeElapsed":163118},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679006983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2784,"timeElapsed":165903},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679009154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2169,"timeElapsed":168074},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679012564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3408,"timeElapsed":171484},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679015415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2849,"timeElapsed":174335},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679017799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2383,"timeElapsed":176719},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679022888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5088,"timeElapsed":181808},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679024679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1789,"timeElapsed":183599},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679042964,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":17147,"timeElapsed":201884},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679047374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":4408,"timeElapsed":206294},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679050950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3574,"timeElapsed":209870},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679053407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2454,"timeElapsed":212327},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679055877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2469,"timeElapsed":214797},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679059098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3220,"timeElapsed":218018},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679060795,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":1695,"timeElapsed":219715},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2743,"timeElapsed":222458},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2479,"timeElapsed":224938},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679073184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5584,"timeElapsed":232104},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679076812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3626,"timeElapsed":235732},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679084392,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7580,"timeElapsed":243312},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679087634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3241,"timeElapsed":246554},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679092364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4728,"timeElapsed":251284},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094836,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2471,"timeElapsed":253756},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679098211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3375,"timeElapsed":257131},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679099957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1744,"timeElapsed":258877},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3853,"timeElapsed":262732},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679105460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1646,"timeElapsed":264380},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679112567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5923,"timeElapsed":271487},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3452,"timeElapsed":274941},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679119171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3149,"timeElapsed":278091},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679122319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3147,"timeElapsed":281239},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679124605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2285,"timeElapsed":283525},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679128652,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4044,"timeElapsed":287571},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679132145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3493,"timeElapsed":291065},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679133602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1456,"timeElapsed":292522},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679136231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2628,"timeElapsed":295151},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679137985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1753,"timeElapsed":296905},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679146741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":7455,"timeElapsed":305661},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679149565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2821,"timeElapsed":308485},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679151753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2186,"timeElapsed":310673},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679154589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2835,"timeElapsed":313509},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679156675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2085,"timeElapsed":315595},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679159631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2954,"timeElapsed":318551},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679161383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1751,"timeElapsed":320303},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679165695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4310,"timeElapsed":324614},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679167339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1643,"timeElapsed":326259},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679175703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6537,"timeElapsed":334623},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679179042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3338,"timeElapsed":337962},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679182147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3104,"timeElapsed":341067},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679184600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2451,"timeElapsed":343520},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679186654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2053,"timeElapsed":345574},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679189452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2797,"timeElapsed":348372},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679191216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1763,"timeElapsed":350136},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679194232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3015,"timeElapsed":353152},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679196244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2010,"timeElapsed":355164},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679204002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":6201,"timeElapsed":362922},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679207405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3400,"timeElapsed":366325},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679210157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2750,"timeElapsed":369076},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3770,"timeElapsed":372848},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679215861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1931,"timeElapsed":374780},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679218480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2619,"timeElapsed":377400},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679221608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3126,"timeElapsed":380528},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679225141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3532,"timeElapsed":384061},{"subjectID":"n5r63w6vzz","prolificID":"63beebaa4c5884797ff00a98","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3c06cabb47273f0c96","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679227222,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2080,"timeElapsed":386142}]